sudoku.com.au 2016-11-04

# Sudoku Puzzles - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is intended to advise you about Sudoku.com.au's protection and use of your personal information. We recommend that you read this policy carefully. 

**Information Collection**  
In general, you can view our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad information for aggregate use. 

**Information and Use**  
Sudoku.com.au will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Our primary use of the information you provide us is for providing you with service(s) requested on our form(s). 

**Sharing of Information**  
We may occasionally partner with another party to provide specific services for us. We will only provide information necessary for the third party to provide these services for us. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We also ask these partners to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours. 

We may occasionally share our customer mailing list with select companies that provide goods or services we think might interest you. The information we provide may include your name and contact information. If you prefer that we not share this information, please send us an email at info@Sudoku.com.au, requesting to be removed from the list. 

**Email Communications**  
We may occasionally send email communications regarding our site, partner offers, special offers or services, products or newsletters. 

You may choose to stop receiving these emails at any time. Information on how to opt out of receiving email is provided with every email, or you may send us an email to info@Sudoku.com.au. Please be sure to include your full name and email address. 

**Links**  
Sudoku.com.au may occasionally contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Sudoku.com.au is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using Sudoku.com.au, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the Sudoku.com.au website following the posting of changes to these terms will be interpreted as your acceptance of those changes.
